(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-21T23:23:58.413893",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
ホロライブファンクラブ！
hololive Official Fan Club!
一条莉々華だよ！
Ichijou Ririka here!
I'm Mori Calliope.
ホロライブファンクラブ、始めました！
We've launched the hololive Official Fan Club!
ここだけのオリジナルグッズやチケット先行抽選、
Exclusive original merchandise, advance ticket lotteries,
他にも楽しいコンテンツがいっぱい！
And lots of other fun content!
Campaigns, too? That sounds really fun. I'm curious.
さあ、みんな、ホロライブファンクラブで一緒に楽しもう！
Now, everyone, let's have fun together in the hololive Official Fan Club!
Join us now!
ここは露天風呂が有名だって言うから、ずっと気になってたんだよね～！
I've been curious about this place because they say its open-air bath is famous!
……ね、キミも一緒に行かない？
...Hey, won't you come with me?
え！？一緒に 入るって意味じゃないよ！？
Huh?! I didn't mean we'd get in together!
おーそーじ！
Big. Big. Clean. Up!
モココ、大掃除やってみたいんだよね！
I want to try this "Big Cleanup" thing!
もちろんキミも一緒にやるんだよ！？
And of course, you'll be joining me!
じゃあ早速、大掃除、開始だ～！
In that case, let the Big cleanup begin!
え～？服のすきまがどうしたって～？
Huh~? What about the gap in my clothes~?
僕が掃除している間に、キミはいったいどこを見てたのかな～？
While I was cleaning, where on earth were you looking~?
おぉ～！ここが夢にまで見た、日本の温泉街～♪
Wow! I've always dreamed of going to Japan's hot springs districts!
ん？もしかして……私と一緒に入りたいな、とか、思ってる？
...What's that look? Are you hoping for the mixed one?
……いいよ、一緒に入ろっか……？
...You know what? Sure, let's go there.
って、やばいやばい！みんな、そろそろカウントダウン始まるよ！
Wait, oh no, oh no! Everyone, the countdown is about to start!
5！
5!
4！
4!
3！
3!
2！
2!
1！
1!
0！
0!
ハッピーニューイヤー！
Happy New Year!
あけましておめでとうございます！今年もよろしくお願いします！
Happy New Year! I look forward to working with you again this year!
えへへ……なんか、改めてかしこまると、恥ずかしくて照れちゃうね♪
Ehehe... It's a bit embarrassing and makes me blush to be so formal like this.
ダイヤモンド富士っていうんだっけ？
Is it called Diamond Fuji?
ほらほら！だんだん富士山の輪郭が見えてきたよ！
Look, look! The silhouette of Mount Fuji is gradually appearing!
なんだかもう、この景色だけで感動するよ～！
I'm already so moved just by this view~!
突然ですが、おせちを作りまーす！
This is sudden, but I'll be making osechi!
つまみ食いしちゃ駄目だよ？
And no sneaking a bite, you hear?
もしつまみ食いしちゃったら……
If you do sneak a bite... Bau wau!
ガブッてしちゃうからね！？
I'll take a big chomp out of you!
おめでとー！おめでとー！キミとぎゅーしながらお祝い♪
Happy New Years! Happy New Years! Celebrating while hugging you!
キミをぎゅーできるのは、モココだけなんだから！
I'm the only one that can hug you, so other people can't copy this!
ほらほら、キミもモココのことぎゅーってして！
C'mon, now it's your turn to hug me back!
せーの、今年もよろしくお願いします！
Ready, set... We look forward to another great year with you!
再販！ゆくホロ2023＆くるホロ2024！
[On-screen: Re-release! YukuHolo 2023 & KuruHolo 2024!]
年末年始デートボイス 参加タレント一覧
[On-screen: New Year's Eve/New Year Date Voice - Participating Talents]
ホロ新春ゲーム祭 2026
[On-screen: Holo New Year Game Festival 2026]
ときのそら
[On-screen: Tokino Sora]
夢の途中の
[On-screen: In the middle of a dream...]
一瞬一瞬を、
[On-screen: ...each and every moment...]
一緒に大切に。
[On-screen: ...cherishing them together.]
過去最大規模の
[On-screen: The largest-scale...]
「そらぱ」がいま始まる。
[On-screen: ...'Sorapa' starts now.]
New Year's Party 2026 「Dream's in Motion」チケット販売中！
[On-screen: New Year's Party 2026 'Dream's in Motion' Tickets on Sale!]
ホロライブ3期生！
Hololive 3rd Generation!
次に挑む舞台は、
The next stage they challenge is...
大作戦？
A grand strategy?
ホロライブ3期生ライブ！
Hololive 3rd Generation Live!
＃きゅるるん大作戦
#KyururunGrandStrategy
〜最強アイドル、推すしかないでしょ〜
~The Strongest Idol, You Have No Choice But to Stan~
「好き」と「かわいい」を詰め込んで、あなたと作る大作戦！
Packed with "love" and "cute," a grand strategy made with you!
いっぱいのこれまでと、ときめくような一瞬を！
With all our "until now," and a heart-fluttering moment!
どこまででも行けちゃう気がする
I feel like we can go absolutely anywhere
2026年1月17日・18日 Ｋアリーナ横浜にて開催！
[On-screen: Held on Jan 17 & 18, 2026, at K-Arena Yokohama!]
ちなみに作戦の内容は...
By the way, the details of the strategy are...
とにかく可愛い！可愛いに満たされろ！
Just purely cute! Be filled with cuteness!
作戦進行中！
Strategy in progress!
＃新春！3期生24時間配信 1月2日(金)20:00〜
[On-screen: New Year! 3rd Generation 24-Hour Live Stream Jan 2 (Fri) 20:00~]
hololive DEV_IS 正月衣装お披露目リレー
[On-screen: hololive DEV_IS New Year Outfit Reveal Relay]
音乃瀬奏
[On-screen: Otonose Kanade]
一条莉々華
[On-screen: Ichijou Ririka]
儒烏風亭らでん
[On-screen: Juufuutei Raden]
轟はじめ
[On-screen: Todoroki Hajime]
響咲リオナ
[On-screen: Isaki Riona]
虎金妃笑虎
[On-screen: Kogane Fiko]
水宮枢
[On-screen: Mizumia Su]
輪堂千速
[On-screen: Rindo Chihaya]
綺々羅々ヴィヴィ
[On-screen: Kikirara Vivi]
1月2日(金)開催 各タレントchにて配信！
[On-screen: Held on Jan 2 (Fri)! Streaming on each talent's channel!]
FLOW GLOW NEW VOICE PACK COMING SOON
[On-screen: FLOW GLOW NEW VOICE PACK COMING SOON]
まもなく配信開始します
[On-screen: Broadcasting starting soon]
hololive COUNTDOWN LIVE 2025 > 2026
FLOW GLOW - FG ROADSTER
Justice - RENEGADE
ReGLOSS - アワータイムイエロー
[ReGLOSS - Our Time Yellow]
Advent - Genesis
hololive Indonesia 3rd Gen - id:entity voices
Secret Society holoX - 暁闇エクスデス
[Secret Society holoX - Dawn Exodus]
Promise - Run Back'Round
hololive Indonesia 2nd Gen - Slap by Step
Myth - Fortune Spinner
hololive 5th Gen - Hyper Jumpin'
hololive Indonesia 1st Gen - Dramatic XVibration
hololive 4th Gen - 青春アーカイブ
[hololive 4th Gen - Seishun Archive]
hololive 3rd Gen - 夢見る空へ
[hololive 3rd Gen - To the Dreaming Sky]
hololive GAMERS - We are GAMERS!!!!
hololive 2nd Gen - キラメキライダー☆
[hololive 2nd Gen - Kirameki Rider☆]
hololive 1st Gen - 電脳ぴゅあ推し大宣言
[hololive 1st Gen - Cyber Pure Oshideclares]
hololive Gen 0 - Shiny Smily Story
and more
hololive production COUNTDOWN LIVE 2025 > 2026
COUNTDOWN LIVE 2026
1st STAGE
This is FLOW GLOW in COUNTDOWN LIVE!
来年もよろしく！ Let's go!
Let's have a great year together next year too! Let's go!
搭載V8エンジン
Equipped with a V8 engine
第7感持ってる原人
A hominid with a 7th sense
ロックするこの世界と全人類
Locking down this world and all of humanity
この5人でゲームチェンジ
With these five, we're gonna change the game
唸る4輪発射せよ
Fire off the roaring four wheels!
皆さんサンキューサランヘヨ
Thank you everyone, saranghaeyo!
操る2台のturntable
Controlling two turntables
獲る1番ここground 0
Taking the number one spot at ground zero
リスク超えて挑戦
Challenging beyond the risks
チャンスもセットだ当然
Of course, opportunity comes as a set
上り上げる頂点
Climbing all the way to the top
座布団積んでく笑点
Stacking up cushions on the comedy show!
乗り込む FG ROADSTER
Climbing into the FG ROADSTER
特殊部隊集合能力者
Special forces, gather up the gifted!
この歴史に名を描く彫刻家
Sculptors carving our names into this history
ぶっちぎりで置き去り後続車
Leaving trailing cars in the dust
今高速でぶち抜いていく大気圏
Now we're breaking through the atmosphere at high speed
エンジンからジェットの炎 揺れている怪気炎
Jet flames from the engine, a roaring wild fire
眼下に広がる大地を 越えていく回帰線
Crossing the tropic line above the earth below
バックミラーにBig Blueが写ってる IBM
Big Blue is in the rearview mirror, IBM
打ち上げ台から飛んでいく
Flying off from the launchpad
うちら世代 この燃料
This is our generation's fuel
朽ち果てないで銀河で
Never rotting away in the galaxy...
寿司食べたい！
I want to eat sushi!
見えているでかいビジョン
I can see the grand vision
燃えているメンバー一同
Every single member is burning hot
ただいま現在進行形
Right now we are in progress
超えてく世界規模
Exceeding the global scale
叶うはずだ Won't stop
It's bound to come true, won't stop
Flow Glow is the place to be
今 chase me
Now chase me
以上、私たちFLOW GLOWでした！
That's all from us, FLOW GLOW!
ここから先も、もっと楽しんでいこう！
Let's keep on having fun after this, too!
tame the fire and fall before my justice
final warning, you know my rage is limitless
on the advent of a new genesis i'm
infamous, yeah i get a little villainous
look into my eyes i'll seek you out
reveal the truth and lies that you just can't hide
clawing at the walls, i feel these sick temptations
what do i have to sacrifice?
bound by a chain, desiring to do it my way
this hurricane of a devastating force is coming
out of my veins, feel my pulse it's rising and igniting
fire snuff it out
walking the line, on the edge of becoming
what i never thought i'd be
better this than a goner
take ' em all out , renegade
Take 'em all out, renegade!
walking the line , fell so far into poison
Walking the line, fell so far into poison...
and i 'm seeing me anew
...and I'm seeing me anew.
got ya , locked and i 'm loaded take ' em all out , renegade
Got ya, locked and I'm loaded, take 'em all out, renegade!
( justice , it 's just like that , i )
(Justice, it's just like that, I)
don't care at all , i 'll fall deeper ' til i can't quit
don't care at all, I'll fall deeper till I can't quit.
never gon ' stop 'cause i don't have a limit
Never gon' stop 'cause I don't have a limit.
my moral compass
is out of focus
renegade , i 'll make it a little wicked
Renegade, I'll make it a little wicked.
the light goes out
make ' em fall down make your , make your last wish
Make 'em fall down, make your, make your last wish
make ' em , make ' em fall down then they crash
Make 'em, make 'em fall down, then they crash
make ' em fall down make your , make your last wish
Make 'em fall down, make your, make your last wish
make ' em , make ' em fall down then they crash
Make 'em, make 'em fall down, then they crash
bound by a vow , can i tread the waters lightly never
Bound by a vow, can I tread the waters lightly, never
making a sound , incognito dio light the pathway
Making a sound, incognito, light the pathway
burning ' em out , in the fallout i 'll stand in the ashes
Burning 'em out, in the fallout, I'll stand in the ashes
fire snuff it out
walking the line , on the edge of becoming
Walking the line on the edge of becoming...
what i never thought i 'd be
...what I never thought I'd be,
better this than a goner
take ' em all out , renegade
Take 'em all out, renegade!
walking the line , fell so far into poison
Walking the line, fell so far into poison...
and i 'm seeing me anew
...and I'm seeing me anew.
got ya , locked and i 'm loaded take ' em all out , renegade
Got ya, locked and I'm loaded, take 'em all out, renegade!
( justice , it 's just like that , i )
(Justice, it's just like that, I)
don't care at all , i 'll fall deeper ' til i can't quit
don't care at all, I'll fall deeper till I can't quit.
never gon ' stop 'cause i don't have a limit
Never gon' stop 'cause I don't have a limit.
my moral compass
is out of focus
renegade , i 'll make it a little wicked
Renegade, I'll make it a little wicked.
the light goes out
tame the fire and fall before my justice
final warning , you know my rage is limitless
Final warning, you know my rage is limitless
on the advent of a new genesis i 'm
On the advent of a new genesis, I'm...
infamous , yeah i get a little villainous
...infamous, yeah, I get a little villainous.
the light goes out
ソラで覚える挑む人生ゲーム
A game of life that we learn by heart and tackle
言い訳めいたハートに従って
Following a heart full of excuses
現実は半即興なプロットです
Reality is a semi-improvised plot
取り憑かれるオーバーな芝居
We're obsessed with over-the-top acting
世渡り上手なあのコはね
That girl who's so good at getting by...
二度と被った猫は外せない
...can never take off her mask of innocence
痛みを知ってしまった magician
A magician who has come to know pain...
手の内は未だ明かせない
...cannot reveal her hand just yet
yellow yellow ゼロからループ
Yellow, yellow, looping from zero
点滅するピリオド
A flashing period
yellow yellow 染まる紅い化粧
Yellow, yellow, dyed in crimson makeup
And what if I can't make or not
たった上 突き放されても
Even if I'm cast aside from above,
No worries! 私には私がついてる
No worries! I've got myself by my side.
酔いが冷めるまで あと少しだけ
Just a little longer until I sober up...
真の愛捉える残像
An afterimage grasping true love,
Slow and steady, we win the race
次の季節を越え Bloom me Bloom me
Beyond the next season, bloom me, bloom me.
どうかこの音を止めないで
Please, don't stop this sound.
Our time Yellow Yellow Let it flow Let it flow ずっと最高を
Our time, Yellow Yellow, let it flow, let it flow, forever at our best.
Our time Yellow Yellow Let it flow Let it flow
Let's enjoy the moment
Look into the mirror 絡まってる蜘蛛の糸
Look into the mirror, tangled in a spider's web.
It happens all the time 躍らされたって Karma's gonna
It happens all the time, even if we are played like puppets, Karma's gonna...
そう、気にしないで 時を編んで明けて暮れて
Yes, don't worry about it, weaving time through day and night.
Always be honest 永遠に変わらないもの
Always be honest, to the things that will never change.
Yellow Yellow 手を取り合えば そこに理由は要らない
Yellow Yellow, if we hold hands, no reasons are needed.
Yellow Yellow 染まる赤い化粧
Yellow Yellow, stained with red makeup.
As my signature, bang bang!
It's not tension, tension... キボウに目を凝らし
It's not tension, tension... keeping our eyes fixed on hope.
創りすぎた運命 人生ごとデリート 新規にリセット
An overdesigned destiny, delete our whole life, start fresh with a reset.
呼ぶ声に導かれ
Guided by the calling voice.
立ち続ける 24/7 終着地は heaven or hell
Standing strong 24/7, destination is heaven or hell.
No time to wait 今だけを信じて 最後のフィナーレまで 灯し進め
No time to wait, believe in only the present, light the way to the grand finale.
酔いが冷めるまで あと少しだけ
Just a little longer until I sober up...
真の愛捉える残像
An afterimage grasping true love,
Slow and steady, we win the race
次の季節を越え Bloom me Bloom me
Beyond the next season, bloom me, bloom me.
どうかこの音を止めないで
Please, don't stop this sound.
Our time Yellow Yellow Let it flow Let it flow ずっと最高を
Our time, Yellow Yellow, let it flow, let it flow, forever at our best.
Our time Yellow Yellow Let it flow Let it flow
Let's enjoy the moment
あけおめー！
Happy New Year!
楽しかったー！
That was so fun!
ReGLOSSでした！バイバーイ！
We were ReGLOSS! Bye-bye!
Time to open up your eyes,
Feel the music start to rise,
Got to break the world and let me in.
I know I was meant to be
Livin' life so fast and free, try to keep your eyes on me,
'Cause this is where my story all begins!
Livin' it up like crazy
Ready to play? Come at me
Carried away so easy,
I can't get enough!
Free as a bird, no limit
Haven't you heard? I'm fearless
Get up and go, let's do this!
Watch me (watch me, watch me, watch me, watch me)
Watch me be your diva,
I'm gonna raise your fever,
Shakin' up all the crowd, making some noise when I'm not allowed,
Livin' my life out loud,
I have awakened to wisdom beyond understanding,
(I keep indulging in my every whim)
Let it out!
Oh, o-oh, o-oh
Don't blame me if I shine too bright
Can't help it if I start a fight
Oh, o-oh, o-oh
Now pay attention, please
'Cause this is only the beginning -
It's our genesis!
Coming to wreak some havoc,
How do you like this plot twist?
I'm embracing my madness.
(Can you hear it?)
Whispers banging down your window
Watch, watch, watch, watch!
Tell me how you like me now.
Let's celebrate the New Year!
Watch, watch, watch, watch...
Let your worries go,
Gonna show you how to lose control.
Ready? You've got to free your mind,
Leave your restraint behind.
Be outrageous,
The chaos is contagious.
Come on, you know what time it is!
It's our genesis!
Time to open up your eyes,
Feel the music start to rise,
Got to break the world and let me in.
I know I was meant to be
Livin' life so fast and free,
Try to keep your eyes on me,
'Cause this is our beginning,
it's our genesis.
Whispers banging down your window,
Rumors reaching a crescendo.
No humble beginnings, I'm destined for great things!
I'm sure you've heard of me by now.
Woah...
Midnight, draw me to the dark side,
Daylight, take me on a joyride.
My crime is my passion,
I'm mayhem in action.
I know what day it is:
This is our genesis.
You know what time it is?
It's our genesis!
Tell me what time it is!
Yeah, you know what time it is?
It's our genesis!
Tell me what time it is!
2nd STAGE
君に届けたい
I want to reach you...
id:entity
だってキミに一歩を踏み出すから
Because I'm taking a step towards you,
おはよう、こんばんは と世界に叫んでみよう
let's shout "Good morning, good evening" to the world!
本日のライブでは どれの自分を見せるの？
Which version of myself will I show in today's live?
前からそう悩んで 好きな自分になれない
I've been worrying about it, unable to become the self I like.
そしてある日誰かに言われた
And then, one day, someone told me...
痛い言葉になんて迷っていた
why was I getting lost in painful words?
いつも 笑顔失わないように
Always trying not to lose my smile,
これ以上は期待を裏切らないと決めた
I decided not to disappoint expectations anymore.
溢れている
Overflowing
雑音の中
in the middle of the noise,
この声響けるか
will this voice be able to resonate?
心に宿る声を聞いてみよう
Let's listen to the voice dwelling inside our hearts.
これはずっと見せたい自分だった
This is the self I've always wanted to show.
集まった声たちが ひとつになる
The gathered voices will become one,
id:entity
月日が過ぎてやっとスポットライトに
Days have passed and I can finally stand in the spotlight,
立てるけれど少しだけ怖くなった
but standing here, I got a little scared.
デモね 一人じゃない 仲間たちがいるんだ
But you see, I'm not alone, I have my friends with me.
家族みたいな絆で違いがわかり合えた
With family-like bonds, we understood each other's differences.
それぞれも
Each and every one of us
輝きがあって
has our own unique shine,
ハーモニー奏でるから
playing a beautiful harmony.
手を繋いで共に夢のその先へ
Let's hold hands and go towards the future of our dreams together.
精一杯歓声を上げましょう
Let's cheer with all our might!
幸せを届けるんだ
We're going to deliver happiness,
どこにだって 響けよ
resonate everywhere!
新しい舞台に飛び込んで
Plunging into a new stage,
今...
now...
ランブララララ to 足取りベンジャラス
Dance, la la la, with dangerous footsteps,
背後隠れた二人にフォーカス
focus on the two hidden behind
やっと見つけた不思議の正体
Finally found the mysterious true identity
きっと恋とは真逆のプログラム
Surely love is a reverse magic program
ただ差し詰めここから行き着くは
In the end, it all leads from here...
あ...
Ah...
アイデンティティ それは希望のアイデンティティ
Identity is the identity of hope
アイデンティティ 唄え 君一人のせい
Identity groans, it's all because of you
まだ捨てないで待って
Don't throw it away yet, wait
それは一つ二つのデスティニー
it's one or two destinies
すぐさまハッピー
Pass by, happy,
落ちる流れ星と歪なあの星
falling shooting stars and that distorted star
重なる面影に寄り添う
Gently nestle up to the overlapping traces
そっと君に寄り添う
Nestle up to you softly
弾けだす視界 胸に飛び込むハート
Jump into the bursting sight, your heart...
刻むあなたのアイデンティティ
carving your identity
Sama-sama, sama-sama!
お疲れ様でした！
Thank you for your hard work!
Sama-sama, sama-sama!
また会う日まで！
Until the day we meet again!
我ら、エデンの星を統べるもの！
We are the rulers of the planet Eden!
秘密結社...
The Secret Society...
holoX!
いっくよー！
Here we go!
時は満ちた！
The time has come!
2026年を待つ貴様ら！
All of you waiting for 2026!
準備はいいかー！
Are you ready?!
おー！
Yeah!
Are you ready?
夜が深まる ほら Darkness
The night deepens, behold, darkness
ノワール ターゲットを奔放で隠す
Noir, hiding the target with wild abandon
縄張りに従え 助手くん
Obey my territory, Joshu-kun!
抜刀 凛々 侍ガール
Drawing sword, dignified, samurai girl!
闇討ちはしないけどな
Though we won't ambush you
ルール違反でしょ？ チェックチェック
That's a rule violation, right? Check, check!
セッションすればOK
If we session, it's OK!
切り拓くでござる ござる
We shall carve our way through, gozaru, gozaru!
悪の手のひら
In the palm of evil's hand,
踊りたくなる
you'll want to dance.
ほら君も
Look, you too...
気づけばノリノリです！
Before you know it, you're grooving!
どうしようもない
It can't be helped,
it can't be helped...
堕ちていく運命
A destiny that's falling...
なす術がない
There is nothing we can do,
もう全部 塗り替えよう
let's repaint everything now!
エクスとエクスとエクスとエクスが
Ex, Ex, Ex, and Ex...
交差する真ん中で
intersect right in the middle,
ネクストネクストネクストネクスト
Next, Next, Next, Next...
世界はもう 始まってる
The world has already begun!
JUMP!
飛びな 飛びな
Fly away, fly away!
闇が呼ぶ方へ
Towards where the darkness calls!
暗黒の
Of the dark...
エクスデス
Exodus!
混沌としたこの世界を、我らholoX色に塗り替えるのだ！
We shall repaint this chaotic world in our holoX colors!
皆の者、勝鬨を上げよ！
Everyone, raise a cry of triumph!
Yes, My Dark!
アブソリュート・ダークネス・インフィニティ！
Absolute Darkness Infinity!
来年こそ世界征服！
World domination next year!
眼光ホークアイ！
Sharp Hawkeye!
はい！今見てる皆さんはもう、holoXerですよ！
Yes, everyone watching now is already a holoXer!
コヨリウム配合！
Koyorium formulated!
2026年もずーっと一緒だよ❤
We'll be together forever in 2026 too!
喰らいなさい！鏡開き！
Take this! Kagamibiraki!
一刀両断！叩き斬る！
Cutting in two with a single stroke! Slashed!
どうしようもない
It can't be helped,
it can't be helped...
堕ちていく運命
A destiny that's falling...
なす術がない
There is nothing we can do,
もう全部 塗り替えよう
let's repaint everything now!
刮目せよ！
Pay close attention!
エクスと
Ex...
エクスが交差する真ん中で
and Ex intersect right in the middle,
ネクストネクストネクストネクスト
Next, Next, Next, Next...
世界はもう 始まってる
The world has already begun!
JUMP!
飛びな 飛びな
Fly away, fly away!
お望み通りに
Just as you wished!
笑うのは
The one who laughs...
holoXで！
Is holoX!
はーはっはっはっは！
Bwahahaha!
しっかり締めるわよ！
Let's wrap this up nicely!
おー！
Yeah!
Run back 'round
Don't stop now
Up with the moonlight
Down in the street lights
Looking for a spotlight
Making my move
Whoa
I'm running
Go on!
Days like a whirlwind
don't stop coming
Got me in a tailspin
What can I do?
Whoa
Keep running!
Go on!!
Lost and found
back to where I started
I won't stay down
trust me, I can do it!
I live life loud
take it to the limit
So stand up proud
now I'm gonna sing it!
Run back 'round
it's a new beginning
I run back 'round
got to keep believing
I know where I'm going
I run back 'round
nothing's gonna stop me now!
I'm gonna run back 'round!
Sparks on the pavement
Dreams in the distance
Gotta be relentless
Faster than sound
Whoah
Keep running!
Go on!!
Locked and loaded 僕らは explosive
Locked and loaded, we are explosive
Swifter and lighter 明日は get brighter
Swifter and lighter, tomorrow is brighter
Faster than lightning 嵐を get excited
Faster than lightning, getting excited in the storm
Come on, are you ready?
It's a new round!
Run back 'round
it's a new beginning
I run back 'round
got to keep believing
I know where I'm going
I run back 'round
nothing's gonna stop me now
Whoa
I'm gonna run back 'round
走って 走って 走って
Running, running, running
I'm gonna run back 'round
始まるよ
It's beginning
Whoa
Look at the dream this way!
I'm gonna run back 'round
Everybody!
Let's go!
We can!
Ready?
Come on!
I'm gonna run back 'round
Whoa
All right, guys, ready?
To greet the new year, Ollie-yah!
No time to waste! Let's get it started!
単純な phrase で catch して
Catch with a simple phrase
困難だらけの人生だけど
It's a difficult life
自由奔放に slap して 楽しんじゃおう
Let's slap freely and enjoy it
Ah oh, ah oh
Fly like a feather, soaring high!
立ちはだかる壁なんて
Facing walls
3秒で knock out
Knock them out in 3 seconds
Fly like a feather, soaring high!
止まらないんじゃなくて
It's not that I won't stop
止まれないんだ！
I can't stop!
Slap by step で空中散歩
Taking a stroll in the air step by step,
私なりで
in my own way.
隙あらばその瞬間に完全掌握
Seizing the moment whenever there's a chance
沼にハマっちゃうぞ！
I'm going to get stuck in the swamp!
One, two, three で深層心理 crash して
Crash into deep psychological layers with one, two, three
ツマらない現実を
Shoot down the boring reality...
常識外れのカラーで
...with unconventional colors,
撃ち抜いて！
shoot through!
Ah 極彩色に染まりたい
Ah, I want to dye myself in vivid colors
ah 極彩色の dance floor
Ah, a multi-colored dance floor
とんだ無礼ね 平手打ちよ
What absolute rudeness, a slap in the face!
子供扱いしないで
Don't treat me like a child
ニヤついた顔に slash it!
Slash that grinning face!
(clap your hands and stand up, please!)
首飛んじゃっても為せば成る
Even if my head flies off, where there's a will, there's a way
それが theory さ
That's the theory!
(clap your hands and stand up, please!)
つべこべ言わず着いてきて
Follow me without making excuses
Ready? It's time for the show
We're ignited
and have no fear
ready to
break through
姿
Though our shapes...
形は
...and forms...
違っても
...may differ,
同じ想いだ
our feelings are the same.
そうだ、だから...
That's right, so...
slap by stepで空中散歩 私なりで
Walking on air, slap by step, in my own way
隙あらばその瞬間に完全掌握
Taking complete control the moment there's an opening
沼にハマっちゃうぞ！
You're gonna fall deep into our swamp!
one two threeで深層心理 crashして
Crashing your deep subconscious on one, two, three
今すぐね
Right now,
私達の色に染め上げた世界を見せる！
we'll show you a world dyed completely in our colors!
皆様、今年の応援もありがとうですわ！
Everyone, thank you so much for your support this year!
ホロIDはもっともっと盛り上がるよ！ずっと見ててね！
HoloID is going to get even more exciting! Keep watching us!
来年もよろしくお願いいたします！
Please look forward to us next year as well!
See you next stage!
hololive production COUNTDOWN LIVE 2025-2026
3rd STAGE
Ahem! 皆さん、もりかりおぺです！
Ahem! Everyone, I'm Mori Calliope!
What's up, hololive English -Myth- coming right at you for a brand new year!
今年すごい盛り上がったね！
This year was so exciting!
来年もよろしく！
Please support us next year too!
We're gonna rock the world ten times harder next year. You in?
Next up, Ina!
Hi, hello everyone! This is Ina!
Thank you so much for a really fun 2025.
今年、凄く楽しかったです！
This year was so much fun!
来年もよろしくお願いしますね！
Please look forward to next year too!
Yeah, let's go! Next is Kiara!
キキリキ！小鳥遊キアラです！
Kikiriki! I'm Takanashi Kiara!
今日もよろしく！盛り上がるぞ！
Let's make this great! Let's hype it up!
Dankeschön! Yes! Come on!
Let's go!
Alright!
Let's have fun in 2026!
Let's go! ガッツリやりましょうか！
Let's go! Let's do this for real!
2026年もよろしくー！
Please support us in 2026 too!
Alright, let's show them what we got!
There's an answer out there somewhere
when the muses whisper "truth or dare?"
The hands of fate play tug-of-war
but no one's keeping score
Stay the course and be tenacious
'cause the future is a game of chance
The chips are down, but I'm all in
I play until I win!
I'm not gonna give up now,
the wheels of fortune circle back around.
A new turn in the betting ring;
a maze of outcomes drawn in golden string.
And through this tangled thread, I see what's up ahead:
A wild chase,
a frantic pace,
I got to try my luck, I'm spinning fate
ah... la da da da da da da
I'm always spinning fate
whoah yeah
Spin the roulette, see where it falls
testing the limits and betting it all
round and around, jumping into the circle
over and over, a test of will
Oh, the game is never easy
and the outcome is a mystery.
But these are fates worth betting on,
their threads unbroken.
Called to life
by flaxen string,
The wheel turns and the die is cast,
The time has come for fate to change at last
And if it's black or red,
I'm moving up ahead
A perfect chance,
a daring dance
I'll spin this thread of fate with my own hands
Ooh la la la
I'm taking fate into my hands
Whoah, yeah
And through this tangled thread, I see what's up ahead
ハイパージャンピンナウ
Hyper Jumpin' Now!
ハイパージャンピン 飛び出そう Walk
Hyper Jumpin', let's leap forward and walk!
Come on baby 輝いて ハートをキュンとパッピラッパ
Come on baby, shine bright and make my heart skip a beat!
ハイパージャンピン 指の先まで
Hyper Jumpin' all the way to our fingertips!
もっともっと刺激が欲しいの
I want more and more excitement!
ハイパージャンピンナウ
Hyper Jumpin' Now!
ハイパージャンピン
Hyper Jumpin'!
今日もツライ？ ハッシュタグがお疲れ様
Is today tough too? The hashtag says "good work today"
テイクアップ！ 空へ這い上がっていくテンション
Take up! The tension is crawling up to the sky!
良いな、動画の売り込みまくるモーション
Nice, the motion of promoting videos like crazy!
カードを乗りこなして進むミッション
The mission is to ride the cards and move forward!
このままスピード 加速して
Keep accelerating the speed just like this
辿り着く先に何があるんだろう
I wonder what lies at our destination
止まらない気持ちは 助走つけて
Take a running start with these unstoppable feelings
次元を越えていこう さあ
Let's cross dimensions, come on!
ハイパージャンピン 飛び跳ねよう
Hyper Jumpin', let's leap!
ハイになって 灰になるまで動じちゃいけない
Get high, we mustn't flinch until we turn to ashes
ハイパージャンピン 空の向こうまで
Hyper Jumpin' all the way to the other side of the sky!
もっともっと近づきたいの
I want to get closer and closer!
Woo oh... ドキドキしたい Give me, give me, give me eyes
Woo oh... I want to feel my heart pounding, give me, give me, give me eyes!
もっともっと高く飛びたいの
I want to jump higher and higher!
ハイパージャンピンナウ
Hyper Jumpin' Now!
ハイパージャンピン
Hyper Jumpin'!
斜めから攻めて解決クエスチョン
Attacking from an angle to solve the question!
ネガティブを切り裂いてくれるセンサー
A sensor that cuts through negativity!
流れるコメントと掛け合いセッション
An interactive session with flowing comments!
エイムを鍛えて狙い撃つフリクション
A friction that trains your aim and shoots!
実はなーなー
Actually, blah blah...
になるのはまーまー
...becoming like that is so-so
邪魔するノイズはかき消せ！ バンバンバン
Drown out the interfering noise! Bang bang bang!
遊びたいだけ！
We just want to play!
味は無視して！
Ignore the taste!
笑い飛ばして！
Laugh it off!
蹴飛ばせ！ キッキング！
Kick it away! Kicking!
トラブルトラブル
Trouble, trouble!
このまま僕らは 旅をして
We continue our journey just like this
辿り着く先に何があるんだろう
I wonder what lies at our destination
信じた未来と リンクして
Linking up with the future we believed in
次元を越えていこう さあ
Let's cross dimensions, come on!
ハイパージャンピン 飛び越えよう
Hyper Jumpin', let's jump over!
ハイになって 灰になるまで動じちゃいけない
Get high, we mustn't flinch until we turn to ashes
ハイパージャンピン 海の向こうまで
Hyper Jumpin' all the way to the other side of the sea!
もっともっと近づきたいの
I want to get closer and closer!
Woo oh... ドキドキしたい Give me, give me, give me eyes
Woo oh... I want to feel my heart pounding, give me, give me, give me eyes!
もっともっと高く飛びたいの
I want to jump higher and higher!
ハイパージャンピンナウ
Hyper Jumpin' Now!
目を覚ませ 目を凝らして
Open your eyes, focus your gaze
夢から抜け出して
Break free from the dream
世界が呼吸開始する
The world begins to breathe
我らの蘇り
Our resurrection...
鏡に映る
Reflected in the mirror...
心に宿っている
dwelling inside my heart...
小さいヒカリ
is a tiny light.
そう、今も感じる
Yes, I still feel it now,
何処かこの奥で
somewhere deep inside...
呼び覚ました
It has awakened.
忘れられない 浮かぶメモリー
Unforgettable memories drift up,
今の自分になる その前に
before I became who I am today.
果てのない 迷路で迷い
Wandering in an endless maze,
そして黄昏が 落ちてくる 何処までも
and the twilight falls, stretching endlessly.
引き締める鎖がまた
The tightening chains once again
身体を止めてた
held my body back.
躊躇いを覚えてしまって
Having learned to hesitate,
凍えてゆくの
I begin to freeze.
明日の向こう側には
On the other side of tomorrow
未知なるエリア
is an unknown area.
その境界線の先に待つのは
What awaits beyond that boundary line
一期の始め
is the beginning of our first era.
目的わからず
Without knowing my purpose,
奈落の底へと
to the bottom of the abyss...
落ちてゆく
I keep falling.
時間さえ知らぬ
Losing even track of time,
時計の針の音
the ticking of the clock hands...
だけが鳴る
is all that echoes.
記憶に残り 広がる海と
Remaining in my memory, the expanding sea and...
何処かの知らない 森の中に
inside some unknown forest.
宇宙を超え 逃げ場探して
Crossing the universe, searching for an escape...
そんな過去もまだ
Even that past still
頭に響いている
resonates inside my head.
解けない鎖を
With the unbreakable chains
断ち切れないまま 藻掻き
still uncut, I struggle.
物語の始まり
The beginning of a story,
探し続けたい
I want to keep searching for.
「51」の不可解な
The baffling riddle of "51,"
謎のようなことさ
is like a mysterious riddle.
この身体の中で目覚めた
Awakening inside this body
本当の姿
is my true self.
運命のカードが占った未来
The future foretold by the card of fate...
もう迷わない
I will hesitate no more.
解き放った鎖が消える
The chains I set free fade away.
進めると信じて
Believing I can move forward,
新たな自分になって
becoming a new version of myself,
光の方へ
toward the light.
ついに辿り着いた
At last, I have arrived at
未知なるエリア
the unknown area.
その境界線を超える日が来た
The day has come to cross that boundary line.
一期の別れ
The parting of our first era.
信じ合う仲間と一緒に
Together with friends who believe in each other,
挑戦の狼煙をあげよう
let's raise the signal fire of challenge.
終わらない
To our never-ending...
青春に
...youth!
boys & girls 羞恥心は捨てて hey jump !
boys & girls, throw away your embarrassment, hey jump!
みんなで揃えば cool jump ! jump !
If we all do it together, cool jump! jump!
フィジカル
Physical strength...
ついてこい 頑張れ
...keep up! Do your best!
青春
Youth...
感じている？ まっすぐ
...are you feeling it? Straight ahead!
成長した姿を見せたい
I want to show how much I've grown.
リハは完璧
The rehearsal was perfect,
本番はもっと全力で
so let's give even more of our all for the real show!
はい はい
Yes! Yes!
大切な思い出
Precious memories...
たくさんあるけれどね まだ
...there are so many, but still...
感傷に浸ってる暇はない
We have no time to be sentimental,
今世紀最大級の夏が始まる
the biggest summer of this century is starting!
Wow...
想像の果てにある高み
The height at the end of our imagination,
Wow...
勝ち獲った景色は尊い
the view we won is so precious.
Wow...
逃げるな 限界の壁 越えて
Don't run away, overcome the wall of limits!
Wow...
僕らはまだチャレンジャー
We are still challengers!
冷たい声に溺れたって
Even if we drown in cold voices,
微かな望みを手繰り寄せるように
as if pulling close a faint hope.
期待外れだと誰かが嘆く
Someone laments that it's disappointing,
期待と痛いがいつも戦う
expectation and pain always fight.
プライドだけを頼りに抗う
Resisting, relying only on our pride,
自分を信じたい
I want to believe in myself.
努力は報われる
Effort is rewarded.
笑いたい奴は笑ってろ
Let whoever wants to laugh, laugh!
感傷に浸ってる暇はない
We have no time to be sentimental,
今世紀最大級の夏が始まる
the biggest summer of this century is starting!
Wow...
反響が足りない もっともっと
The echo is not enough, more and more!
Wow...
後悔はさせない
I won't let you regret it!
Wow...
想像の果てにある高み
The height at the end of our imagination,
Wow...
勝ち獲った景色は尊い
the view we won is so precious.
Wow...
逃げるな 限界の壁 越えて
Don't run away, overcome the wall of limits!
Wow...
僕らはまだチャレンジャー
We are still challengers!
Wow...
夢見る空へ
[Song: Dreaming Skyward]
重ねた手はギュッと離さずに
Our overlapping hands, hold them tight and don't let go.
いくよ 行こう
Let's go, let's go!
夢見る空へ
To the dreaming sky.
窓越しに見上げた
Looking up through the window...
とても小さな空
...at the very tiny sky.
ここで出会えたのは
Meeting each other here...
数え切れない奇跡
...is a miracle beyond count.
繰り返した一歩が
Each repeated step...
きらめきを繋いで
...connected the sparkle,
星のような笑顔
and a smile like a star...
導いた
...guided us.
Day by day みんなの声が
Day by day, if I can hear everyone's voices...
聞こえたら力になる
...it gives me strength.
Stage by stage ここで
Stage by stage, right here...
それぞれ目指すもの
...what each of us aims for,
それぞれ描くもの
what each of us draws,
それぞれ願う夢
and the dream each of us wishes for.
重ねた手はギュッと離さずに
Our overlapping hands, hold them tight and don't let go.
ひとりひとり違う色で描く
Each and every one of us painting in different colors.
走り出すときめき
The running excitement,
振り向くことなく真っすぐに
straight ahead without looking back.
いくよ 行こう
Let's go, let's go!
夢見る空へ
To the dreaming sky.
笑いあったことや
The times we laughed together,
尽きそうにない話題
and the endless topics to talk about...
思い出いっぱいなのに
...even though we have so many memories.
あっという間の日々
In the blink of an eye, these days...
上書きじゃなくって
...instead of overwriting them,
名前つけて保存
I'll save them with a new name.
どれも全部大事って
I can confidently say
言い切れる
that each and every one is precious.
One for all
みんなの声が力になる
Everyone's voices become my strength.
All for all
今日もにぎやかすぎるくらい
Today is so lively,
笑顔がもう止まらない
that I can't stop smiling.
想いはふくらんでいく
My feelings keep growing.
重ねた今 ぎゅっとかみしめた
Now, I tightly cherish the moments we've built up.
ひとり（ひとり）違う（声で）歌声は広がる
With our individual, unique voices, our singing spreads.
風を感じたらまっすぐに
Once we feel the wind, we'll head straight on.
行くよ！（行こう！）夢見る空へ
Here we go! (Let's go!) To the dreaming sky.
“憧れ”へ手を伸ばし
Reaching out toward our aspirations,
つかみとったその光が
the light we've grabbed hold of...
いつの日か
...will someday...
また誰かの“憧れ”に変わる
...turn into someone else's aspiration.
つなげよう
Let's connect them!
重ねた手はぎゅっと離さずに
Keep our hands tightly held together,
ひとり（ひとり）違う（色で）描き出すときめき
with each of our unique colors, painting our excitement.
出会った全てにありがとう
Thank you for everything we've encountered.
キセキ（だって）起こし（続け）
We will continue to make miracles happen.
ずっと（ずっと）そばにいるよ
I'll always, always be by your side.
行くよ！（行こう！）夢見る空へ
Here we go! (Let's go!) To the dreaming sky.
ホロライブゲーマーズ！
Hololive Gamers!
おまたせ！白上フブキだよ！
Sorry to keep you waiting! It's Shirakami Fubuki!
みんなおまたせ！
Everyone, sorry to keep you waiting!
We are GAMERS!!!!
楽しむ準備は？
Are you ready to have fun?
できてるよね！
You're ready, right?!
せーの、We are GAMERS!!!!
Ready, set, We are GAMERS!!!!
フブキ！Go!
Fubuki! Go!
こーんと狐が登場 白髪ケモミミ白上フブキです
With a 'kon', a fox appears! I'm the white-haired, beast-eared Shirakami Fubuki.
突っ込んでちゃ始まらない 君もすこん部に入部しなさい
If you just play straight-man, nothing will start! You should join the Sukon-bu too!
はい！ (Yeah!) はい！ (Yeah!)
Hi! (Yeah!) Hi! (Yeah!)
古今東西コーン茶をちょーだい
From east to west, give me some corn tea!
AIじゃないし得意はMC
I'm not an AI, and my specialty is MCing!
赤い恋より金のコイが推し
Rather than 'red love', I'm all about the 'golden carp'!
ミオしゃー！
Miosha!
うち うち うちだよ 大神ミオだよ 黒髪ケモミミ狼（みおーん！）
It's me, me, me, Ookami Mio! A black-haired, beast-eared wolf! (Mioon!)
ツッコミで止めます ライブ配信
I'll keep things in line with my straight-man remarks! Live streaming...
笑い出すと止まらない ゲラゲラ
...once I start laughing, I can't stop! Giga-gaga!
つまり実はPONってコト？
Wait, does that mean I'm actually a klutz?
小足ステップしちゃう音
The sound of quick-foot steps!
タロット占いで見る未来
Looking at the future with tarot card readings!
ホラーゲームはやりたくなーい！
I don't want to play horror games!
4人揃えばゲーマーズ最強 君も遊ぼうよBダッシュ
When the four of us are together, Gamers are the strongest! Let's play together, B-dash!
クリア目指してレベル上げ 今日は何プレイしよう
Levelling up to clear the game! What should we play today?
君のハートも攻略しちゃう
We're going to conquer your heart as well!
選択をしてシミュレーション 初見も古参も対よろ
Make a choice for the simulation! Newcomers and veterans, pleased to meet you!
やっぱりゲームは楽しいね
After all, gaming is so much fun!
G-A-M-E-R-S We are GAMERS!!!!
G-A-M-E-R-S
おかゆー！
Okayu!
いっくよー もぐもぐ〜猫又おかゆ おにぎりおにぎり はいっどうぞー
Here we go, munch munch~ Nekomata Okayu! Here's an onigiri for you!
きらきらふらふらしょーない猫だもん ふーんそっかぁ 僕でよくない？
A sparkling, drifting, helpless cat. Hmm, is that so? Wouldn't I be just fine?
まったりゆっくり跳ねるリズム
A laidback, slow, bouncing rhythm.
全肯定するおかゆイズム
An all-accepting 'Okayu-ism'.
全工程効率OK
All steps and efficiency are OK!
毎日僕といっ〜しょ！
Spend every single day with me!
ころね！
Korone!
おあよー！ゆびゆびワンワン！ パンをコネコネ戌神ころね
Good morning! Yubi-yubi, woof woof! Kneading bread, I'm Inugami Korone!
犬種：キャバリア・キング・チャールズ・スパニエル 懐くけど圧かける
Breed: Cavalier King Charles Spaniel! I'll grow fond of you, but I'll also pressure you!
訛るイントネーション 割れるリアクション
An accented intonation and loud reactions!
まずは指を捧げてくれる？配信ショー
First, will you offer up your fingers? Welcome to my stream!
わがったなーほーね 指示厨おけ
Understood, I see! backseat gamers are welcome!
好物のレトロゲーお届け
Delivering my favorite retro games to you!
4人揃えば ゲーマーズ最強
When the four of us gather, Gamers are the strongest!
フラグが立てばすぐ回収
We trigger every flag right away.
エイム鍛えて狙い撃ち
We train our aim and take the shot.
今日は何プレイしよう
What should we play today?
君のハートも回復しちゃう
I'll restore your heart as well!
ワクワクするね このダンジョン
This dungeon is so exciting!
耐久っていうか止められない
It's an endurance stream, or rather, we can't stop!
だってゲームが好きなんだもん
Because we just love games so much!
突然ですが、ボーナスチャレンジの時間です。
All of a sudden, it's time for the bonus challenge!
大きな声でレスポンスして、高得点を狙いましょう！
Call back in a loud voice and aim for a high score!
Are you ready?
せーの！ こーん こん！
One, two! Kon, kon!
こーん こん！
Kon, kon!
せーの！ みおーん みおん！
One, two! Mioon, mion!
みおーん みおん！
Mioon, mion!
せーの！ もぐもぐ！
One, two! Mogu, mogu!
もぐもぐ！
Mogu, mogu!
せーの！ ゆびゆび！
One, two! Yubi, yubi!
ゆびゆび！
Yubi, yubi!
せーの！ こーん こん！
One, two! Kon, kon!
こーん こん！
Kon, kon!
せーの！ みおーん みおん！
One, two! Mioon, mion!
みおーん みおん！
Mioon, mion!
せーの！ もぐもぐ！
One, two! Mogu, mogu!
もぐもぐ！
Mogu, mogu!
せーの！ ゆびゆび！
One, two! Yubi, yubi!
ゆびゆび！
Yubi, yubi!
Perfect!
おー！
Oh!
4人揃えば ゲーマーズ最強
When the four of us gather, Gamers are the strongest!
上手くいかなくても コンティニュー
Even if things don't go well, continue!
全クリするまで諦めない
We won't give up until we get 100% completion!
エンディングを見に行こう
Let's go see the ending!
君のハートも攻略しちゃう
We'll conquer your heart too!
選択をしてシミュレーション
Make your choice and run the simulation!
初見も古参も対よろ
Whether you're new or an old-timer, GLHF!
やっぱりゲームは楽しいね
After all, gaming is so much fun!
WE ARE GAMERS!!!!
こうして2025年の幕が閉じるのであった
And so, the curtain closed on the year 2025...
生まれたてのドキドキを響かせよう
Let's make our fresh heartbeats resound!
最高の時間 最高の仲間と
With the best time and the best friends,
キラメキに乗って
riding on the sparkle!
イェーイ！
Yeah!
覚えてるかな？ 最初の歌
Do you remember? Our very first song...
懐かしいね
How nostalgic...
私 声が 震えていた
My voice was trembling...
ほんの少し
Just a little bit...
あの日のから 続く未来は
The future continuing from that day...
みんなと掴んだ今日だよ
is the "today" we grasped together with everyone!
もっともっともっともっと 加速するハート
More, more, more, more, our hearts accelerate!
一緒に
Together...
行くよ どこまでも
we'll go anywhere!
Are you ready?
準備はOK？
Are you set to go?
ひらけ！夢の扉を
Open up! The door to our dreams!
一、二、三
One, two, three!
キラメキライダー
Sparkling Rider!
生まれたてのドキドキを響かせよう
Let's make our fresh heartbeats resound!
最高の時間 最高の仲間と
With the best time and the best friends,
ここにいるよ 見つけてくれたから
I am right here, because you found me!
君に会いたくてやってきたんだ みんなで歌おう
I wanted to see you, so I came here! Let's all sing together!
終わらないメロディー
This never-ending melody...
キラメキに乗って
riding on the sparkle!
届いてるかな？ 私の声
Is it reaching you? My voice...
ハッキリと
Loud and clear...
届けたいのは 君に笑顔
What I want to deliver is a smile to you...
そのスマイル
that smile of yours!
理想の遠さに悔しくて
Frustrated by how far our ideals seemed,
みんなと泣き笑ったね
we laughed and cried together with everyone!
ぎゅっとぎゅっとぎゅっとぎゅっと 全て抱きしめて
Squeeze, squeeze, squeeze, squeeze, embrace it all!
一緒に
Together...
行こう どこまでも
let's go anywhere!
Are you ready?
準備はOK？
Are you set to go?
すすめ！希望の道を
Forward! On the path of hope!
一、二、三
One, two, three!
キラメキライダー
Sparkling Rider!
好きな気持ち カラフルに奏でたいな
I want to play my love for this colorfully!
最高の場所 最高のみんなと
In the best place, with the best people!
ここにいるよ 幻なんかじゃない
I am right here, it's not an illusion!
...じゃない
...not an illusion.
君の心が幸せに染まるように
So that your heart is painted with happiness,
重ねていくハーモニー
our layered harmony...
キラメキ纏って
Clad in sparkles!
歌い続けたいな
I want to keep on singing,
踊り続けたいな
I want to keep on dancing.
そんな願いやわがままもいいでしょ？
Surely a selfish wish like that is okay, right?
だって楽しすぎて！
Because it's just too much fun!
もうとまらない！！
I can't stop anymore!
輝くステージで
On this shining stage,
もっともっと！！
even more, even more!
お願い
Please,
ずっと！！
forever!!
嬉しい楽しい愛しいだけじゃ語れない
Joy, fun, and love alone aren't enough to describe it,
今も今も悩みはあるけど
even though I still have worries even now.
ここにいるよ私
I'm right here,
ここにいるよ
I'm standing right here!
君と同じ世界を
Staring at the same world
見つめて
as you...
行くよ？
Ready?
キラメキライダー☆
Kirameki Rider☆
生まれたてのドキドキを響かせよう
Let's make our fresh heartbeats echo!
最高の時間最高の仲間と
With the best of times and the best of friends,
ここにいるよ見つけてくれたから
I'm right here, because you found me.
君に会いたくてやって来たんだみんなで歌おう
I came here because I wanted to see you, let's all sing!
終わらないメロディ
A never-ending melody,
キラメキに乗って☆
riding on the sparkles☆
キラメキ纏って
clad in sparkles...
イェーイ！
Yay!
2025年もあと少し！みんな盛り上がってるー？
2025 is almost over! Is everyone hyped?
今回はカウントダウンライブ！
This is the Countdown Live!
あれ？あれれー？
Huh? Wait a minute...
コメントの熱量、なんだか少なくない？
The comment hype is looking a bit low, isn't it?
まだまだ足りないぞ、こんなの！
This is not nearly enough!
いくぞー！
Let's go!
このこのこのこの
Like this, like this, like this, like this!
他推しは許しません
Supporting other idols is unforgivable!
私だけに集中してね
Focus only on me!
私だけに一途に
Devoted only to me...
ちゅーしなきゃやだやだぴゅあちゅー
If you don't pledge your love, no way, pure love!
ちゅっちゅっちゅちょーだい
Give me kisses!
ぷんぷんぷんぷんちょちょちょちょーだいも
Pout, pout, pout, pout, give me some too!
よそ見したらぷんぷんぷんめ！
If you look away, I'll get super angry!
めろめろめらっほっぺ膨らむ
Head over heels, my cheeks puff up,
ぴゅあ推しにしましょうあっぷっぷーぷいっ
Make me your pure oshi! Puff, puff, hmph!
他推しはダメ、まさかいいわけないでしょ
Other oshis are bad, surely you knew that?
他推しはダメ、本当にいやいや
Other oshis are bad, I really hate it!
いつでも見てて、私待ってる
Always watch me, I'm waiting!
あなたが教えてくれた愛情のテンプラ！
The tempura of love that you taught me!
私を支える栄養素
The nutrients that support me!
らぶらぶらぶち四六時中ちゅっちゅ
Love love love, kissing 24/7!
とってもとってもとってもとっても愛してほしい
I want you to love me so, so, so, so much!
はっぴーはっぴーはっぴーで最上級ぎゅっぎゅ
With happy happy happy, the highest class of hugs!
はっきりはっきりはっきりはっきりはっきりはっきりはっきり
Clearly, clearly, clearly, clearly, clearly, clearly, clearly!
もっとアピールしてピコピコ気持ちのバロメーターが超上がる
Appeal to me more! My beep-beep feelings barometer is rising like crazy!
推して推して推して
Support me, support me, support me!
もっともっともっともっと、私のこと推してね
Support me more, more, more, more!
おーいみんな！ここまでついて来れてる？
Hey everyone! Can you keep up so far?
この後も、この調子でいくよー！
Let's keep going like this for the rest!
うりゃおい！うりゃおい！うりゃおい！うりゃおい！
Urya-oi! Urya-oi! Urya-oi! Urya-oi!
他推しはダメ、ほかの子のほっぺに
Other oshis are bad! To another girl's cheeks...
よそ見は浮気、ちゅっちゅっちゅ
Looking away is cheating! Kiss, kiss, kiss!
私以外を見ているでしょう？
You're looking at someone other than me, aren't you?
ありえないの、ありえない！
That's unbelievable, unbelievable!
ぷんぷん怒る子に、ちゅっちゅっちゅっちゅ届けて
Deliver kisses to the angry, pouting girl!
よそ見したよね？嘘、マジ無理です！
You looked away, didn't you? No way, I really can't deal with that!
他推しは怒っちゃう、私を推すんじゃ！
Other oshis make me mad, you have to support me!
指切りしてよ、針千本！
Make a pinky promise, swallow a thousand needles!
心変わりしたら本当に
If you have a change of heart, I will really...
拗ねる、怒る、泣いちゃうからね！
pout, get mad, and cry!
他推しはしないでね
Don't support other oshis!
私だけに、尽くしてね
Devote yourself only to me!
だってほらコメントが愛に溢れている
Look, the comments are overflowing with love!
私のHP、みるみる回復！
My HP is recovering right before my eyes!
ちゅっちゅっちゅ、ちゅっちゅっちゅ、わーちゃー！
Chu, chu, chu, chu, chu, chu, wah-cha!
ごめごめごめちょ、ごめごめごめちょ！
Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry!
らぶらぶらぶち四六時中ちゅっちゅ
Love love love, kissing 24/7!
いっぱい いっぱい いっぱい、愛してほしい
I want you to love me so, so, so much!
はっぴーはっぴーはっぴーで最上級ぎゅっぎゅ
With happy happy happy, the highest class of hugs!
うっとりうっとり
Entranced, entranced...
こりにこりにこりにこり
Kori, kori, kori, kori!
毎日の糧 チミチミお仕事励んでくれてありがとう
Thank you for working so hard, bit by bit, for your daily bread!
愛おしい 愛おしい
So lovely, so precious!
絶対絶対絶対絶対絶対絶対絶対絶対！
Absolutely, absolutely, absolutely!
おねだりね
Pretty please!
このこのこのこの
This one, this one, this one, this one!
うー このこのこのこの
Ooh, this one, this one, this one, this one!
このこのこのこの このー！
This one, this one, this one, this one, this one!
銀河の果てまで おしおしおーし！
Oshi, oshi, oshi to the ends of the galaxy!
同じ未来を見ていたい
I want to look at the same future
あの夢手にしたい
I want to grasp that dream
それぞれ違った
With our own different...
ココロで
...hearts,
走れgo!
let's run, go!
Shiny Smily Story
どこを見ても真っ暗な場所に芽生えてた
Sprouting in a place of pitch-black darkness wherever I looked,
ほんの小さな希望に
by a tiny shred of hope,
この瞳奪われた
my eyes were completely captivated.
不安で揺れる心をうまくチューニングして
Tuning my heart that trembles with anxiety,
ほんの小さな勇気を振り絞っていたよ
I was squeezing out every bit of my tiny courage.
諦めの文字デリートして進む
Deleting the word "giving up" as I move forward,
苦しいときも
even in painful times,
もうわたしはひとりじゃないから
because I am not alone anymore.
だから
So...
もっと夢追いかけたい
I want to chase my dreams even more,
ワクワク止まらない
the excitement just won't stop!
想像超えてく
Going beyond our imagination,
世界見せてあげる
I will show you the world!
アクセスしてみたい？
Do you want to access it?
後悔なんてそうさせない
I won't let you have any regrets!
それぞれ違った
With our own different...
ココロで
...hearts,
走れgo!
let's run, go!
仮想の空に輝く眩しい想いは
These dazzling feelings shining in the virtual sky
見たことのない光をリアルに届けるよ
will deliver an unseen light into reality.
いつも聞こえるエールはここにキャプチャーして
Capturing the cheers we always hear right here,
また新しい光を探したくなるよ
it makes me want to search for a new light again.
君の笑顔は保存して進む
Saving your smile as I move forward,
悲しいときに
in times of sadness,
見返すよ力が湧くから
I will look back at it, because it gives me strength.
だから
So...
胸を張って夢追いかけたい
With heads held high, I want to chase my dreams,
奇跡のストーリー
this miraculous story!
一緒に作ろう
Let's create together
終わらない夢を
an endless dream.
誰一人欠かせない
Not a single person is expendable,
愛が舞ったこの世界
in this world where love has danced.
それぞれ違った
With our own different...
ココロで
...hearts,
彩れ！
let's color it in!
悲しいときも
Even in sad times,
寂しいときも
even in lonely times,
信じ合えるものがある
there is something we can believe in together.
忘れずにこの鼓動鳴らし続けたい
Without forgetting, I want to keep this heartbeat sounding out.
終わらない世界に溢れ出すよ笑顔達
In this endless world, smiles will overflow!
笑顔達
Smiles...
憧れの舞台立ちたい
I want to stand on the stage of my dreams
らしく輝きたい
and shine in my own way.
ときに涙して
Sometimes crying tears,
また笑い合いたい
I want to laugh together again.
同じ未来を見たい
I want to look at the same future
あの夢手にしたい
and grasp that dream.
踏み出そう
Let's take a step forward,
奇跡の一歩を
this miraculous step!
息切らして夢追いかけたい
Out of breath, I want to chase my dreams,
ワクワク止まらない
the excitement just won't stop!
想像超えてく
Going beyond our imagination,
世界見せてあげる
I will show you the world!
アクセスしてみたい？
Do you want to access it?
後悔なんてここにない
There are no regrets here!
それぞれ違った
With our own different...
ココロで
...hearts,
作るworld
we will create our world!
みんな！コークは持ったかな？
Everyone! Do you have your Cokes?
持ちました！乾杯する！
Got it! Let's toast!
こらこら！早いよラプちゃん！
Hey, hey! Too early, Lapu-chan!
避けるな！
Don't dodge!
当たる！
It'll hit!
年越しのタイミングでみんなで『乾杯』ってするんだよ
We all say "Cheers" together at the turn of the year.
やだやだ！もう喉カラカラ！
No, no! My throat is already parched!
ふふ、楽しみだね！
Hehe, I can't wait!
ね？みこさん？みこさん？
Right, Miko-san? Miko-san?
ひゃっはー！いいライブだったねー！
Hyahha! That was a great live show!
お疲れい！
Good job!
この後どうする？ご飯食べる？
What should we do next? Grab some food?
いや、どこも混んでんじゃない？
Nah, won't everywhere be crowded?
確かにー
True.
お家帰りますかね。あ、運転手さん、まっすぐね
Guess we're going home. Oh, driver, go straight.
おっおっおっ…？
Oh, oh, oh...?
あれ？お前ら！？
Huh? You guys?!
何帰ってんだー！！！
Why are you going home?!!!
乾杯！乾杯！
Cheers! Cheers!
フブちゃん達がついてきてる
Fubu-chan and the others are following us.
おろおろ、フブさん、寂しくなっちゃったのかな？
Oh dear, did Fubu-san get lonely?
おーーい！！！
Ooooi!!!
なんか怒ってない？
Aren't they angry?
あれ？やばい。あの悪戯がバレたかな？
Huh? Uh oh. Did they find out about that prank?
あはは！やりすぎだったっかなー？
Ahaha! Did we go too far?
やばいかも…運転手さん、ごめん！
This might be bad... Driver, sorry!
うわー！
Uwah!
みこがドラテクで逃げ切るぞ！
Miko will escape using her pro driving techniques!
わおー！わおー！
Wao! Wao!
あ、来た！
Ah, they're here!
おらおらおら！
Go go go!
すごーい、すごーい！
Amazing, amazing!
フブさんごめんて！もう悪戯しないから！
Fubu-san, I'm sorry! We won't play pranks anymore!
だめだよ、みこみこん。反省しなさい
No good, Miko-Miko. You must reflect.
お前も共犯だろうが！
But you were an accomplice!
何の話だ？
What are you talking about?
二人とも、これ持って
You two, hold this.
何するの？
What are we doing?
もうすぐ新年だよ！
It's almost the New Year!
おーー！
Ohhh!
10！9！
10! 9!
8！7！
8! 7!
6！5！
6! 5!
4！3！
4! 3!
2！1！
2! 1!
乾杯！！！
Cheers!!!
あけましておめでとう！
Happy New Year!
わわわわわ…
Gulp gulp gulp...
今年もよろしくね！
Look forward to this year too!
かんぱーい！
Cheers!
そういえば、悪戯って何なの？
By the way, what was the prank anyway?
あ、それね。フブちゃんのおへそ、増やしたんだよ<
Ah, that. We multiplied Fubu-chan's belly button.
ぎょふっ！？
Gyofu?!
この後はコカ・コーラと一緒に、スペシャルライブステージ！
Up next, along with Coca-Cola, a Special Live Stage!
そうさずっと！僕らの奇跡が
Yes, forever! May our miracle...
途切れないように歌うんだ
...never end, so we will sing.
もっと高く！大きな声で
Even higher! With a loud voice!
きこえてた？何かが始まるサイン
Did you hear it? The sign that something is starting.
集まって気づけば
Before we knew it, we gathered...
和音(コード)を奏でた
...and played a chord.
夢に見るだけじゃもう足りないでしょ？
Just dreaming isn't enough anymore, right?
キミを待ってる世界があるよ
There's a world out there waiting for you.
楽しい予感にほら
Look, with this fun premonition,
飛び乗っちゃえばいい
you should just jump right in.
トキメキは止められないから
Because this excitement cannot be stopped,
走ろう！
let's run!
つれて行くよ！光の真ん中
I'll take you to the center of the light,
夢の先へ
beyond our dreams!
羽ばたける勇気はキミの願い
The courage to flap our wings is your wish.
皆でつないだこの奇跡が
This miracle we've connected together...
途切れないように歌うんだ
...may it never end, so we will sing.
もっと高く！大きな声で
Even higher! With a loud voice!
答えとか理屈にまどわされて
Bewildered by answers and logic,
さまよっても戻ってこれる場所があったんだ
even if we wander, there was a place we could return to.
地図にない道ゆく僕らの旅
Our journey on a path not found on any map,
願いだけが道標だよ<
only our wishes are our guideposts.
夢の色がかわっても
Even if the colors of our dreams change,
かわらないメロディー
this melody remains unchanged.
キミのために僕らのために歌おう！
Let's sing for you, for us!
そうさきっと！
Yes, surely!
僕らの奇跡は終わらないよ
Our miracle will never end.
涙さえキッカケにかえていこう
Let's turn even our tears into a new beginning.
信じてくれる仲間と一緒に
Together with the friends who believe in us,
どこへだって飛び出して行こう
let's fly out anywhere!
もっと遠く！
Even further!
届けて
Deliver it
いっせーのーで！
Ready, set, go!
未来の僕らに まだ見ぬ君に
To our future selves and to you whom we haven't met yet
伝えたいこと 沢山あるんだ
There are so many things we want to convey
迎えたイマは 当たり前なんかじゃない
The present we've welcomed is not something to take for granted
翼を広げ さあ今
Spread your wings, right now
飛ぼう！
Let's fly!
take my hand！！
Take my hand!
連れて行くよ！ 光の真ん中 夢の先へ
We'll take you! To the center of the light, beyond our dreams
羽ばたける勇気は キミの願い
The courage to spread your wings is your wish
皆で繋いだ この奇跡が
This miracle we've woven together
途切れないように 歌うんだ もっと高く！
We'll keep singing so it never gets interrupted, higher!
大きな声で
With a louder voice
僕らの未来 彩って
Adorn our future
どこまでも響け！ prism melody
Resound everywhere! Prism melody
Show Them (Who You Are)
Won't you just forget about the past?
Cause in time it will never matter
But the love we had
I'm hoping it will last
Bersama kita t'lah lewati
Together we have passed through
Tawa dan canda jadi memori
Laughter and jokes turning into memories
Pastikan artinya kan cerahkanmu nanti
Make sure its meaning will brighten you later
To do what you were meant to do
For it's time to make it true
Together we can always stand
Your hand in my hand
Forever hand in hand
Tuk mulai bermimpi
To start dreaming
Genggamlah yang kau cari
Grasp what you are looking for
Teriakkan...
Shout it out...
La la la la la, la la la la la
Kau takkan sendiri
You won't be alone
It's time to show them who you are
Just shout it from the mountain high
To the sky we go, we go
Bersama kita t'lah lewati
Together we have passed through
Tawa dan canda jadi memori
Laughter and jokes turning into memories
Pastikan artinya cerahkanmu nanti
Make sure its meaning will brighten you later
Cerahkanmu nanti
Brighten you later
To do what you were meant to do
For it's time to make it true
Together we can always stand
Your hand in my hand
Forever hand in hand
Tuk mulai bermimpi
To start dreaming
Genggamlah yang kau cari
Grasp what you are looking for
Teriakkan...
Shout it out...
La la la la la, la la la la la
Kau takkan sendiri
You won't be alone
So go and travel far
Run and show them who you are
I'll be singing
La la la la la, la la la la la
Be who you meant to be
Jangan kau takut
Don't you be afraid
Karena pada akhirnya semua 'kan baik saja
Because in the end everything will be just fine
頑張ろう！
Let's do our best!
Jangan kau takut
Don't you be afraid
Karena pada akhirnya
Because in the end,
Semua 'kan baik saja
everything will be just fine.
Arahkan pandangan mu
Turn your gaze
Tajam lurus ke depan
straight ahead.
'Tuk mulai bermimpi
To start dreaming,
Genggam lah yang kau cari
hold onto what you seek.
Teriakkan, "La la la la la, la la la la la"
Shout it out: "La-la-la-la-la, la-la-la-la-la!"
Kau takkan sendiri
You won't be alone.
So go and travel far
Run and show them who you are
I'll be singing, "La la la la la, la la la la la"
I'll be singing: "La-la-la-la-la, la-la-la-la-la!"
Kau takkan sendiri
You won't be alone.
It's time to show them who you are
Just shout it from the mountain high
To the sky we go, we go
[オン・スクリーン・テキスト: All for One]
[On-Screen Text: All for One]
Ooh...
Just look around and see, it's so incredible!
So many smiles in a sea of light
Take one step with me and you'll be dazzled,
There's magic in the air tonight
The hours zoom zoom zoom
My heart goes boom boom boom
The world is brighter because you believe in me
Let's shout it loud loud loud
Our time is right now
We're on the edge of destiny
For a moment, I can dream with you
Every miracle we hoped for might come true
We come together, reaching out from far and wide,
And suddenly, you're here by my side!
When our voices and hearts unite,
we're gonna shine bright!
Together, we're all for one
Let's sing! All for one!
The thrill of happiness is all around us!
Jump in, 'cause it's all for one
Let's sing! All for one!
We're on our way to good times, good vibes
We'll treasure this day the rest of our lives
Hey!
All that we waited for,
the dream we're striving toward,
We're singing, all for one!
All for one!
Everything's in motion,
Get up and start the celebration,
Come see the wonders here beyond imagination
We're joining hands for the world to see
Feel the love and the energy!
The hours zoom zoom zoom
My heart goes boom boom boom
A dizzy whirlwind of dreams and reality
Let's shout it loud loud loud
Our time is right now
We're here together, finally!
Every moment takes my breath away;
There's a feeling here that words cannot convey,
We hear the rhythm and we rise to meet the song,
And suddenly, our hearts beat as one!
Every voice ringing loud and clear,
so glad to be here
Together, we're all for one
Let's sing! All for one!
We'll sing in harmony and we'll be happy
Jump in, 'cause it's all for one
Let's sing! All for one!
Keep up the hype, it's good times good vibes
Remember this night the rest of our lives
Hey!
Raise up your hands and sway,
your light will lead our way,
We're shining, all for one!
All for one!
So bring your memories, your joy and your hope,
We'll gather and we'll sing upon this endless road, oh, oh
Feel the music in your passionate soul,
We're here right now, so let the good times roll, oh, oh
Every time that I'm with you,
I could swear it's like a wish is coming true
So I'll believe in you if you believe in me,
Together we can chase all our dreams!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5!
When our voices and hearts unite,
we're gonna shine bright!
Together, we're all for one
Let's sing! All for one!
The thrill of happiness is all around us!
Jump in, 'cause it's all for one
Let's sing! All for one!
We're on our way to good times, good vibes
We'll treasure this day the rest of our lives
Hey!
All that we waited for,
the dream we're striving toward,
We're singing, all for one!
All for One!
皆さん あけましておめでとうございます！
Happy New Year, everyone!
おめでとう！
Happy New Year!
Reach to the top, we are...
ReGLOSS!
ここからはホロライブDEV_ISコラボステージです！
From here on is the hololive DEV_IS collab stage!
聴いてください、FG ROADSTER by ReGLOSS！
Please listen to: FG ROADSTER by ReGLOSS!
Let's go!
搭載 V8エンジン 第七感持ってる現在
V8 engine under the hood, currently possessing a seventh sense
ロックするこの世界から全身全霊
From this locked-on world with all our heart and soul
この5人でゲームをチェンジ
We five are going to change the game
唸る四輪走っちゃって
Roaring four wheels, speeding away
皆さん サンキュー 三番手
Thank you everyone, third place
迫る二体のタンデム
Two tight tandems closing in
獲る一番ココからだ
Taking the number one spot starts right here
限界超えて挑戦
Challenging beyond our limits
チャンスもセットだ当然
Opportunities are included, of course
登りあげる頂点
Climbing all the way to the peak
アクセル踏んでくショータイム
Stepping on the gas, it's showtime
乗り込め FG ROADSTER
Climb in, FG ROADSTER
プッシュボタン始動 能力差
Push-button start, showcasing our skill difference
この歴史名乗るコックピット
In this cockpit of historic renown
ぶっちぎり置き去り高速
Tearing ahead, leaving them behind at high speed
インコース切り抜けチェイス 喰い足りてねぇ
Cutting through the inside lane in this chase, still not satisfied
エンジンかジェットの咆哮 揺れている回帰線
The roar of the engine or jet, shaking tropic lines
眼下に広がる大地を超えてく航海記
Travelogue sailing beyond the lands spread out below
バックミラーにビッグブルーが映ってる I will do my way
With Big Blue reflecting in the rearview mirror, I will do my way
打ち明けたいから飛んでく 打ち鳴らせ打鍵
I fly because I want to open up, play the keyboard
門出の銘 ぶち破っていくです
Smashing the inscription of our fresh start
フィンガレス シスターズビート
Fingerless sisters beat
見上げればデカいビジョン 燃えてるメンバー一堂
Looking up at a huge vision, all the burning members gathered
ただいま現在進行形 越えてく世界規模
Right now, in progress, we are going global
火花弾き出すロードスター 心臓がもっと
Sparking roadster, heart beating even faster
エリアに満ちていく咆哮
The roar filling the area
FG走り出す
FG starts running
光るピストン ロードスター
Glowing piston, roadster
ヘビリーブースター 目覚めてく本能は
Heavy booster, the awakening instinct is
青い炎
a blue flame
BFF, let's go out
届けに行く風に乗って ゼロから宇宙まで
Going to deliver, riding the wind, from zero to space
飛び乗れ 走るFGロードスター 唸るブースター
Jump on and run, FG Roadster, roaring booster
ロー、ミドル、ハイ 飛ばすスピード
Low, middle, high, speeding away
今 チェイスミー
Chase me now
あけましておめでとうございます！
Happy New Year!
ここからは私たちFLOW GLOWが、ReGLOSS先輩のフィーリングラデーションをカバーさせていただきます！
From here on, we, FLOW GLOW, will cover ReGLOSS-senpais' "Feeling Graduation"!
にこたんが来た！
Nikotan is here!
セクシーにいくぞ！しょっぴしょわ！
Going sexy! Shoppishowa!
DEV_IS界レッツゴー！
DEV_IS world, let's go!
甘酒ちゃん、負けてらんない！
Amazake-chan, we can't lose!
びび！
Bibi!
私の元に、おいで！
Come to me!
Ah, oh...
One, half, stop 刻むインナービート 紐解く私 集中
One, half, stop, carving the inner beat, unraveling myself, concentrating
さあ 巡り巡るステップ ショータイム 全然悪くない イマジネーション
Now, step showtime going round and round, a completely fine imagination
世界中のチャイムは鳴り渡って 悲しみには別れを告げ
Chimes all over the world ring out, saying goodbye to sadness
酸いも甘いも宇宙に放り出して 滲む空響くバラ色を
Throwing sweets and sours out into space, the rose color echoing in the blurred sky
どれだけ幕見せようとしても 君がいなければ何にもない
No matter how much of the act I try to show, without you, there's nothing
微かな傷すらつかない嘘 針の糸 繋いで交差
A lie that doesn't even leave a faint scratch, connecting the needle's thread and intersecting
アザレア色 追い風にして
Making the azalea color our tailwind
Come on, let's go!
強く吹き荒れる向かい風にも心 満たされて
Even against the strong blowing headwind, my heart is fulfilled
飛び立って To the future
Flying off to the future
何周したってオールライト Mr. Light
No matter how many laps, it's alright, Mr. Light
遠い未来目指し進めば 瞬く間に広がる解放区
If we head toward the distant future, in the blink of an eye, the liberated zone spreads
一つ一つ全てがドラマ 街が見上げれば Mr. Light
Each and every thing is drama, when the city looks up, Mr. Light
変わり変わる彩るパノラマ 満ち溢れる フィーリングラデーション
The shifting, colorful panorama, overflowing with feeling gradation
飛び立って You and me
Flying off, you and me
恐れるものは何もない Mr. Light
There is nothing to fear, Mr. Light
綺麗な朝焼けが ほら目の前に広がっているよ
Look, a beautiful sunrise is spreading out before our eyes
Mr. Light!
Ah, ah...
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
最後の曲は！
The last song is!
Our Bright Parade!
Yeah!
Parade, Parade, Parade!
輝くんだよ
We will shine!
呼び合う声を合図に
With our voices calling out as our signal
Parade, Parade, Parade!
探しにゆく
I'm going to look for it...
スタートは 何度だって
We can start over as many times as we like!
ただ 独り言を綴った
I just wrote down my soliloquy,
ただ 始まりたくて 走った
I just ran, wanting things to begin.
遠く 暗がりに灯った
Lit up far away in the darkness,
それは 眩し過ぎた名前
it was a name far too bright.
それは 優し過ぎる思い出
Those memories are far too kind,
もっと 近づけと 手を伸ばした
so I reached out my hand to get closer.
思いがけず 結び合った
Unexpectedly, we became tied together.
ほら 今
Look, now,
迷子は “僕等” になった
the lost children have become "us."
Parade, Parade, Parade!
輝くんだよ
We are shining!
悔しさも 愛しさも 連れておいで
Bring both your regrets and your love with you.
風、夢、羽 飛び立てるさ
Wind, dreams, and wings—we can fly away!
ささやかな祈りは 光
Our modest prayers are light,
終わりなき 兆し
an endless sign of what's to come.
君を 見つけたこと 胸を張れるよ
I can be proud that I found you.
ここから これから Our Bright Parade, Parade!
From here, from now on, Our Bright Parade, Parade!
まだ 頼りない予感を
With this still unreliable premonition,
歌おう 恥ずかしくなんて ないよ
let's sing! There's absolutely nothing to be embarrassed about.
誰も解けない イマジナリー
An imaginary world that no one else can decipher,
いつかまた逢える おまじない
it's a good luck charm that we will meet again someday.
あの日ゼロに始まった ストーリー
The story that started from zero on that day.
数え切れない 言の葉
Countless words,
数えるような 想いじゃないさ
these feelings aren't something you can just count.
ほら 今
Look, now,
“僕等”を 一つと呼ぼう
let's call "us" one!
Parade, Parade, Parade!
美しいんだよ
It is beautiful!
許し合える刹那
Fleeting moments of mutual understanding,
夜は きらめく
the night sparkles.
雨、晴れ、カレイド またとない空
Rain, shine, and a kaleidoscope under a unique sky.
相応しい旅路とは
The journey most suited for us
君と在ることさ
is being with you.
君と在ることなんだ
Yes, it is being with you.
“ただいま” を聞けば
When I hear "I'm home,"
“おかえり” って叫ぶ よ
I'll shout back, "welcome home!"
当たり前じゃないか
Isn't that only natural?
Parade, Parade, Parade!
輝くんだよ
We are shining!
暗がりを 満たすのは
The ones filling the darkness
君 だ 僕 だ！
are you and me!
Parade, Parade, Parade!
輝くんだよ
We are shining!
悔しさも 愛しさも 連れておいで
Bring both your regrets and your love with you.
風、夢、羽 飛び立てるさ
Wind, dreams, and wings—we can fly away!
ささやかな祈りは 光
Our modest prayers are light,
終わりなき 兆し
an endless sign of what's to come.
君と 飛び込んでゆく 素敵なスタートさ
Diving in together with you, it's a wonderful start!
ここから これから Our Bright Parade, Parade!
From here, from now on, Our Bright Parade, Parade!
Our Bright Parade, Parade!
この後は もう1本グランプリ！
2026年もホロライブプロダクションをよろしくお願い致します！
Next up is the "One More" Grand Prix!
Please continue to support hololive production in 2026!